Guide to the Time Inc. People Publishing and Business Records 1973-2003 MS 3009-RG 27
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Publisher Richard Durrell Files, 1973-1983; 56.25 Linear feet in 57 record cartons
  - Subseries I.B. Subject Files, 1973-1983; 55.25 Linear feet in 56 record cartons
    - Media Industry Newsletter (MIN), 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 23)
    - Media Workshop, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 24)
    - Memoranda: Arnold, Kerry, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 25)
    - Memoranda: Barnet, Bruce, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 26)
    - Memoranda: Crawford, Clare, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 27)
    - Memoranda: Crowley, John, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 28)
    - Memoranda: Crutcher, Larry, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 29)
    - Memoranda: Davidson, Ralph, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 30)
    - Memoranda: Donovan, Hedley, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 31)
    - Memoranda: Dunne, Bill, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 32)
    - Memoranda: Edit, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 33)
    - Memoranda: Edwards, Bari, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 34)
    - Memoranda: Elliman, Don, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 35-37)
    - Memoranda: Fisler, Bob, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 38)
    - Memoranda: Gallagher, John, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 39)
    - Memoranda: Hale, Paul, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 40)
    - Memoranda: Hall, Bill, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 41)
    - Memoranda: Hall, Bill, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda: Heiskell, Andrew, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda: Jones, Charlotte, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda: Keylor, Art, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda: Labich, Dick, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda: Larsen, Roy, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda: Lund, Chuck, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda: McCluskey, Jim, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda: Mulcahy, Eileen, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda: Nunes, Lucy, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda: Posthorn, Stan, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 12-13)
    - Memoranda: Pouliot, Ruth, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda: Production, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda: Schenck, John, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 16)
    - Memoranda: Schiller, Clark, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 17)
    - Memoranda: Schrieber, Bob, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 18)
    - Memoranda: Slovinsky, Lou, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda: Stoklos, Mary, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 20)
    - Memoranda: Stolley, Dick, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 21)
    - Memoranda: Strauss, Ed, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 22-23)
    - Memoranda: Sutton, Kelso, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 24)
    - Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 25-26)
    - Memoranda: Valk, Garry, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 27)
    - Memoranda: Znachko, Mike, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 28)
    - Memoranda: Zucchi, Dan, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 29-31)
    - Money, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 32)
    - Merchandising, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 33)
    - Monger and Waterhouse, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 34)
    - National Association of Broadcasters Presentation, 1978 (Offsite-box 2957, Folder 35)
    - Nashville Weekend: October 13-15, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 1)
    - National Enquirer, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 2)
    - National Golf Links, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 3)
    - National Star, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 4)
    - New Orleans, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 5)
    - New York Times, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 6)
    - Newsweek, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 7)
    - NOVA Magazine, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 8)
    - Parties, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 9)
    - Parties: For Charlotte Schiff Jones: June, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 10)
    - Parties: December 3 Party at Home, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 11)
    - People Shopper, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 12)
    - People to People, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 13)
    - Permissions, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 14)
    - Personnel, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 15-16)
    - Personnel: Restructure, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 17)
    - Photographers, Etc., 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 18)
    - Photo Show, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 19)
    - Pioneer Press, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 20)
    - Positioning, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 21)
    - Postal Service, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 22)
    - Posters, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 23)
    - Presentation Film, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 24)
    - Presentations: People's Choice: November 1, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 25)
    - Price Tests, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 26)
    - Pricing: Regulations, Tests, Etc., 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 27)
    - Print: Plants, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 28)
    - Production, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 29)
    - Production: Corporate, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 30)
    - Production: Weekly Meetings, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 31)
    - Promotion: Air, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 32-33)
    - Promotion: Consumer Circulation, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 34)
    - Promotion: Consumer Radio, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 35)
    - Promotion: General, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 36)
    - Promotion: Print, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 37)
    - Promotion: Trades, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 38)
    - Publicity: Air, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 39)
    - Publishers' Lunch, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 40)
    - Raises, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 41)
    - Rates, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 42)
    - RDA, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 43)
    - Reader's Digest, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 44)
    - Rebates: Advertising Complaints, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 45)
    - Recession, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 46)
    - Redbook, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 47)
    - Regional and Metro, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 48)
    - Reprints, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 49)
    - Research by Young & Rubicam: Tests, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 50)
    - Rate Increase, 1978 (Offsite-box 2958, Folder 51)
    - Research, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 1)
    - Research: Focus Groups, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 2-3)
    - Research: Scarborough Study, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 4)
    - Result Stories, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 5)
    - Sales Figures, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 6)
    - Sales Meeting: Sawgrass: May 9-12, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 7)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Durrell, Dick, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 8)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Lund, Chuck, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 9)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 10)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Posthorn, Stan, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 11)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Schenck, John, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 12)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 13)
    - Screenings, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 14)
    - Screenings: A Chorus Line: Chicago: January 9, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 15)
    - Screenings: Grease: June 15, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 16)
    - Select Magazines, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 17)
    - Shopping Lists (Inserts), 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 18)
    - Simmons, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 19)
    - Special Units, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 20)
    - Speeches: Minnesota Advertising Federation: January 19, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 21)
    - Speeches: International Periodical Distributors Association: November 30, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 22)
    - Sports Illustrated, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 23)
    - Starch, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 24)
    - Store Checks, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 25)
    - Store Checks by Ad Salesmen, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 26)
    - Subscriptions, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 27)
    - Supermarket News, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 28)
    - Tanglewood, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 29)
    - Target Group Index, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 30)
    - Television and Television Shows, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 31)
    - Television: David Susskind Show, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 32)
    - Television: People Show: Share of Market, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 33)
    - Temple-Eastex, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 34)
    - Time, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 35)
    - Time Distribution Services: A & P, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 36)
    - Time Distribution Services: Checkout, 1978 (Offsite-box 2959, Folder 37)
    - Time Distribution Services: Correspondence, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 1)
    - Time Distribution Services: Draw, Sale, Etc., 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 2)
    - Time Distribution Services: Front End, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 3)
    - Time Distribution Services: General, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 4)
    - Time Distribution Services: People, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 5)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 6)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meeting: Regional Managers: Dallas: March 28-29, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 7)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meeting: Los Angeles: September 22, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 8)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meeting: Disney World: December 3-7, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 9)
    - Time Distribution Services: Personnel, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 10)
    - Time Distribution Services: Racking, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 11)
    - Time Distribution Services: Safeway, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 12)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stop and Shop (Louis Banks), 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 13)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 14)
    - Time Distribution Services: Weingarten, Lufkin, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 15)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 16)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers: Cities Off Certification, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 17)
    - Time Distribution Services: Winn-Dixie, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 18)
    - Time-Life Books, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 19)
    - Time-Life Films, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 20)
    - Trades, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 21)
    - Travel Category, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 22)
    - Trips: Fishing, Tennis, Etc., 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 23)
    - TV Guide, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 24)
    - United Fund, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 25)
    - US, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 26)
    - US: Advertising, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 27)
    - US: Circulation, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 28)
    - US: Promotion, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 29)
    - US: Publicity, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 30)
    - US: Racking [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 31)
    - US: Research, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 32)
    - US: Sales Figures, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 33)
    - Washington Star, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 34)
    - Weekly Report: Keylor, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 35)
    - Woman's Day, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 36)
    - Women, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 37)
    - Year-End Issue, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 38)
    - Young & Rubicam Promotion, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 39)
    - Branch Offices: Chicago, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 40)
    - Branch Offices: Denver, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 41)
    - Branch Offices: Detroit, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 42)
    - Branch Offices: Los Angeles, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 43)
    - Branch Offices: Minneapolis, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 44)
    - Branch Offices: New York, 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 45)
    - Branch Offices: Washington, D.C., 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 46)
    - Branch Offices: West Coast (General), 1978 (Offsite-box 2960, Folder 47)
    - Advertising Age, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 1)
    - Ad Council, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 2)
    - Advertising/Edit Ratio, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 3)
    - Airline Research, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 4)
    - Airline Subs, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 5)
    - Airport Sales, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 6)
    - American Advertising Federation, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 8)
    - Anny, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 9)
    - Apparel Category, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 10)
    - Applications, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 11)
    - Automotive Strike, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 12)
    - Awards, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 13)
    - Bleed, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 14)
    - Blynn, Buz, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 15)
    - Budget, 1979 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 27-28)
    - Budgets: Ad Sales, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 16)
    - Budgets: Circulation, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 17)
    - Budgets: Edit, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 18)
    - Budgets and Five Year Plan, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 19)
    - Budgets: General, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 20)
    - Budgets: Production, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 21)
    - Budgets: Promotion, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 22)
    - Cable Television, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 23)
    - Canada, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 24)
    - Circulation, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 25)
    - Circulation: All Magazines, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 26)
    - Clips: People, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 27-28)
    - Clips: People: Carter Statement, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 29-30)
    - College Market, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 31)
    - Company Plane, 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 32)
    - Complaints: Advertising, Etc., 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 33)
    - Complaints: Subs, Edits, Etc., 1979 (Offsite-box 2961, Folder 34)
    - Comp Lists, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 1)
    - Conferences: Northwestern University: April 27-28, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 2)
    - Conferences: Conference on Anti Trust: Washington, D.C.: May 6-8, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 3)
    - Conventions: Trade, Etc., 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 4)
    - Conventions: Dinners, Luncheons, Etc., 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 5)
    - Conventions: Detroit Auto Show: January 12, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 6)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Boca Raton: January 23, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 7)
    - Conventions: Cosmetic, Toiletry, and Fragrance Association: Boca Raton: February 25-March 1, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 8)
    - Conventions: Western Association of Food Chains: Honolulu: April 7-11, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 9)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Dallas: May 6-9, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 10)
    - Conventions: American Association Of Advertising: Greenbrier: May 16-19, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 11)
    - Conventions: ACT Accolade: Philadelphia: August 15, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 12)
    - Conventions: National Association of Convenience Stores: New Orleans: September 14-15, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 13)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Washington, D.C.: October 14-16, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 14)
    - Conventions: American Society of Travel Agents: Munich: October 21-26, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 15)
    - Conventions: American Advertising Federation: Phoenix: November 9, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 16)
    - Copy Acceptance, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 17)
    - Copy Processing: Decentralization, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 18)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 19)
    - Cosmopolitan, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 20)
    - Covers, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 22)
    - Covers: Tests and Research, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 23)
    - Covers: Tip Ons, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 24)
    - Couponing, 1979 (Offsite-box 2962, Folder 21)
    - CPM, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 1)
    - Distribution, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 2)
    - Douglas, Mike Show: Los Angeles: November 12, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 3)
    - Edit: Serious Articles, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 4)
    - Family Circle, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 5)
    - Fifth Anniversary, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 6)
    - Filler Space, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 7)
    - Filler Space: Others in People, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 8)
    - Folio, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 9)
    - Fortune, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 10)
    - Free Contribution Requests, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 11)
    - Free Space Requests, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 12)
    - Free Sub Requests, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 13)
    - Gallagher Report, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 14)
    - Golf, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 15)
    - Golf: Legends of Golf: Austin: April 24-25, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 16)
    - Golf: National Golf Links: May 15-16, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 17)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Golf Invitational: Detroit: May 21, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 18)
    - Golf: National Golf Links: July 11-12, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 19)
    - Golf: Golden Lights Pro-Am: May 29-30, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 20)
    - Golf: Detroit: June 19, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 21)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Golf Invitational: June 25-26, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 22)
    - Golf: National Golf Links: Retailers: July 19, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 23)
    - Golf: Chicago: September 17, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 24)
    - Golf: National Golf Links: September 19-20, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 25)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Invitational: Palm Springs: December 6-8, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 26)
    - Hall Magazine Editorial Representation, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 27)
    - Hold, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 28)
    - Home Broadcasting Office (HBO), 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 29)
    - Ibit, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 30)
    - Ideas (For People), 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 31)
    - Ideas: Airborn Audio Systems, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 32)
    - Ideas: Radio: Murray Roberts, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 33)
    - Ideas: Warner Paperback, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 34)
    - International, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 35)
    - International: England, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 36)
    - International: Germany, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 37)
    - International: Japan, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 38)
    - Inserts, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 39)
    - Insert Cards, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 40)
    - Intercorporate Group, 1979 (Offsite-box 2963, Folder 41)
    - Legal, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Logo, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Trademark, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 3)
    - Letters, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 4)
    - Letters: Circulation Complaints, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 5)
    - Letters: Complaints On Stories, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 6)
    - Letters: Miscellaneous, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 7)
    - Letters: Northland College, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 8-9)
    - Letters: Per Person vs. Billing, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 10)
    - Letters: Personal, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 11)
    - Letters: Personal [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R42)
    - Letters: Personal: Pen Tudor and Arthritis Foundation, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 12)
    - Letters: Personal Stocks, Etc., 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 13)
    - Letters: Personal Stocks, Etc. [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R42)
    - Letters: Requests for Story Coverage, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 14)
    - Letters: To Personnel, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 15)
    - Licensing, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 16)
    - Life, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 17)
    - Liquor Category, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 18)
    - Look, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 19)
    - Look: Panel Estimates, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 20)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Agencies, Advertisers, Etc., 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 21)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Marine Dinner: Washington, D.C.: June 12, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 22)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Saratoga Outing: August 9, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 23)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Arjay Miller: San Francisco: August 21, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 24)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Henry Kissinger: October 2, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 25)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Clare Booth Luce: October 9, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 26)
    - Magazine Research Inc., 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 27)
    - Magazines, Tabloids, Newspapers, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 28)
    - Magazines, Tabloids, Newspapers: New, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 29)
    - Mailing Lists, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 30)
    - Mailings: Diary, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 31)
    - Meeting: Anti-Trust Review: June 1, 1979 (Offsite-box 2964, Folder 32)
    - Meeting: Northland College, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda: Barnet, Bruce, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda: Cooper, Mike, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda: Crawford, Clare, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda: Crowley, John, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda: Crutcher, Larry, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda: Davidson, Ralph, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda: D'Onofrio, Pat: Share of Market Report, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda: Donovan, Hedley, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda: Edit, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda: Fisler, Bob, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda: Gallagher, John, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda: Gentalen, Tiit, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Keylor, Art, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda: Labich, Dick, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda: Larsen, Roy, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 16)
    - Memoranda: Lund, Chuck, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 17)
    - Memoranda: Marketing Services, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 18)
    - Memoranda: McCluskey, Jim, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda: Meigher, Chris, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 20)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 21)
    - Memoranda: Mulcahy, Eileen, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 22)
    - Memoranda: Nunes, Lucy, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 23)
    - Memoranda: Posthorn, Stan, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 24)
    - Memoranda: Pouliot, Ruth, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 25)
    - Memoranda: Publicity, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 26)
    - Memoranda: Schenck, John, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 27)
    - Memoranda: Schiller, Clark, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 28)
    - Memoranda: Slovinsky, Lou, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 29)
    - Memoranda: Stokley, Mary, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 30)
    - Memoranda: Stolley, Dick, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 31)
    - Memoranda: Strauss, Ed, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 32-33)
    - Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 34-35)
    - Memoranda: Thorkilsen, Eric, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 36-37)
    - Memoranda: Verdon, John, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 38)
    - Memoranda: Znachko, Mike, 1979 (Offsite-box 2965, Folder 39)
    - Memoranda: Zucchi, Dan, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 1-2)
    - Merchandising, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 4)
    - Monger and Waterhouse, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 5)
    - Motion Picture Industry: Category, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 6)